http://www.newsreader-project.eu/ontologies/ORG	http://dbpedia.org/ontology/Organisation
http://www.newsreader-project.eu/ontologies/PER	http://dbpedia.org/ontology/Person
http://www.newsreader-project.eu/ontologies/LOC	http://dbpedia.org/ontology/Place
http://www.newsreader-project.eu/ontologies/MISC http://dbpedia.org/ontology/MISC
http://www.newsreader-project.eu/ontologies/ORGANISATION	http://dbpedia.org/ontology/Organisation
http://www.newsreader-project.eu/ontologies/PERSON	http://dbpedia.org/ontology/Person
http://www.newsreader-project.eu/ontologies/LOCATION	http://dbpedia.org/ontology/Place
http://www.newsreader-project.eu/ontologies/MISCELANEOUS http://dbpedia.org/ontology/MISC
